It's an AI powered recruiting assistant to streamline the hiring process with intelligent automation and data driven insights.
So let's start from a quick question.
Hey, what you can do?
Oh, it can help us in creating JDs, screening candidates, sending emails, developing assessments and went like into a show during and off.
So let's start by creating a new JD.
So he's asking about some details.
So I guess we got some incident credits.
I'll do a quick recharge.
So I have zero credits.
I'll try to buy some credits.
Yes, so I think my credits are updated.
If I don't crash.
Yeah.
So the guy can start.
So I think the JD mission has been started.
We'll take a little time because like there is a process of generation that is happening here.
Yes, we got it.
Yeah.
So as you can see all the details, whether it's a liberal department, experience girls qualifications, pretty much a very good JD.
Also, if I want, I can modify something.
But we'll skip it.
So we can publish this JD also.
It will be published to the characters career pages.
So that anyone can comment apply.
Now let me proceed with the screening candidates for this journey as they have created and published the journey.
The candidates will apply and now we can screen the candidates.
I should continue.
Now I need to approach as much as you are.
We can approach as many as we want.
Just I'm uploading less because we need to be quickly.
So the AI is analyzing the candidates.
It will take a little time.
So we got the scores for the software engineer.
We can click and see what the profile experience.
We can get an insight of that particular whether it was a personal type of match for experience for educational background for projects.
And then a summary of the entire resume.
Like that's a very detailed analysis of the resume we can see over here.
We also have some filters to like adjust and see how the resume can apply and rescreen on the basis of these fields.
Like what's awaited what what is awaited if we want to get to any of these keys.
So let's subtraction.
Now reject for them.
Select selected.
So the rejected candidates will get a rejection.
We can continue the next process.
So after the screen of candidates we can start with assessments or we can directly conduct a review if you want.
I'll start with assessments.
So we can create different types of resume whether it's cognitive or scale or task.
We can like create any of these three or we can create all of these three whatever we want.
And we can conduct that in a sequential manner.
So let's start with cognitive assessment.
I'll select TV level for take time.
I will select that.
The resume will be 10 questions.
I said 10.
Just to be quick.
So we've got some cognitive questions of verbal and RC if that's passage.
Then we have a question for passage.
Okay.
And that's an RC or big RC.
Then we have the logical reasoning questions.
The critical reasoning question abstract and all.
We have enough standard cognitive assessment.
Yeah.
So this minute I've been catered.
Now I can send this into the candidates that I have accepted like after the screening.
So let's send this assessment.
So it's asking which assessment I want to send as after cognitive as an assessment.
The email I can send to the shortest candidates.
I think that could have accepted.
I like to see if the same.
Okay.
So yeah.
What an email with the different details, position, time, duration.
And then I can send this one from here.
Right.
But don't be once in a while.
I think that was a visual with my.
Well, basically.
Let's start with this one.
So we have a question.
This is the passage.
Then I have a question.
Select this.
Select some random options.
Let's see how much I score.
To mission the living.
I guess.
I see my questions.
Well, so much for this one.
So first thing.
So this one has been conducted now as the husband is completed.
I can now shortlist the candidates for whatever the next one that I want to conduct.
So I want to open it next time within the skill assessment.
So I will proceed with shortlisting for the skill assessment.
So like the flow is very simple.
Like supposedly conducted an assessment.
Now we have to you, you would choose like what should be our next round.
It could be another assessment on what it would be an interview round.
So I'll just take start with one more assessment.
Or I think I should shortlist first.
So I'll just turn once the red line is passes.
You can proceed with shortlisting candidates for the next one.
The red line is passed.
I'll shortlist the candidates for next.
So I try to asking you which round you want to generate a shortlisting report.
So I would say now that I want to conduct an assessment round.
So I will generate that.
So it's generating the report of the failure assessment that I have conducted,
which was cooperative assessment.
Yeah, so we could have scored only 10%.
So here we can see the statistics of the candidates.
I would score the highest for the lowest four.
Also the scores for individual candidates too.
In the business of this, we can decide like what should be our shortlisting criteria.
It could be either a score based or it could be a count based.
Suppose I want to sort list of one candidate to get at that.
So if I want to sort list candidates have scored our specific percentage.
If I say suppose it's 20 between the 10 of days,
suppose it's 98.
It could be either of these two.
I would say it's a shortlist top one.
So the candidates would be shortlisted in the next round.
So this was the cognitive report.
Now, yeah, one candidate has been successfully listed.
Now I can create a skill assessment and send it to the shortlisted candidate
for a skill assessment round.
Very simple.
I think complicated.
So we can create a skill assessment now.
I will do it easy to look back.
Now I can come to that skills.
I can add these skills for this job description that I have of AI engineer.
That should be software engineer.
The assessment is being generated.
So for the skill assessment, what we do for each skill,
we scrape the web.
We get some points for that particular.
So suppose I'm generating a question for Python,
then it will skip the web at some better context of the Python.
It could be questions.
It could be some theory or practice problems.
And it will generate questions on the basis of that.
So like very good quality questions we would get here.
Yeah.
So this was medium level assessment.
Now I can proceed with.
So it is saying, let me know if you want to send the assessment email.
Yeah, I want to send the assessment email to the candidates.
I have shortlisted the candidates before.
So the assessment will be sent to those candidates
who have shortlisted for the skill assessment.
Yeah.
So I was asking whether it's a skill or not.
It's a skill.
So yeah.
I've been sent to the shortlisted candidates.
They will receive the link, I guess.
So I got the assessment.
But I'll start at same.
Like I did the common investment.
I can do the skill assessment too.
Login.
Keeping.
Star.
This one is submitted.
So now.
So now I can decide what should be my next round.
It could be either task placement that we have over here
or it could be an interview round.
I'll proceed with task.